<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string-array name="fortune_results">
        <item>Your ability for accomplishment will follow with success.</item>
        <item>You will be traveling and coming into a fortune.</item>
        <item>An enjoyable vacation is awaiting you.</item>
        <item>You will soon discover how truly fortunate you really are.</item>
        <item>Use your ability at this time to stay focused on your goal. You will succeed.</item>
        <item>Your respect for others will be your ticket to success.</item>
        <item>Don\'t worry about the stock market. Invest in family.</item>
        <item>Be patient and love will find you when you least expect it.</item>
        <item>Your life is trouble free.</item>
        <item>You will obtain your goal if you maintain your course.</item>
        <item>Treat yourself to something of quality.</item>
        <item>You will make a sudden rise in life.</item>
        <item>Many admire your social and physical appearance.</item>
        <item>You will always be surrounded by true friends.</item>
        <item>Prosperity is in your future.</item>
        <item>You are deep thinker with a knack for solving problem.</item>
        <item>You will be selected for a promotion because of your accomplishments.</item>
        <item>People find it difficult to resist your persuasive manner.</item>
        <item>Your kindness will lead you to happiness.</item>
        <item>When love and skill works together, expect a masterpiece.</item>
        <item>You are in good hand.</item>
        <item>Your ability for accomplishment will follow with success.</item>
        <item>You will have many friends when you need them.</item>
        <item>You will be called to fill a position of high honor and responsibility.</item>
        <item>You will win success in whatever calling you adopt.</item>
        <item>You will never need to worry about a steady income.</item>
        <item>Your past success will be overshadowed by your future successes.</item>
        <item>Your past success will be overshadowed by your future successes.</item>
        <item>A financial investment will yield return beyond your wildest hopes.</item>
        <item>You will be fortunate in everything you put your hands on.</item>
        <item>Your love life will be happy and harmonious.</item>
        <item>Your future will be happy and productive.</item>
    </string-array>
</resources>